hitechanalogy.com 2012-06-23

# Privacy | Hitechanalogy

**Privacy Policy:**

We welcome your voice and advice since both are equally honorable for us. So do not hesitate to contact with us for your quarries about our Privacy Policy by sending an email at [info@hitechanalogy.com](mailto:info@hitechanalogy.com).

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance at [www.hitechanalogy.com](http://www.hitechanalogy.com/). Our Privacy Policy documents the types of information received and collected at [www.hitechanalogy.com](http://www.hitechanalogy.com/) and how this information is used and protected.

 **Log Files:**  
We also use log files as all other web sites do. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons:**  
[www.hitechanalogy.com](http://www.hitechanalogy.com/) also uses Cookies and Web Beacons in order to have a record of information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages t he user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browsers.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie** :  
Our Ads Partner Google, as a third party vendor, also uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

It also uses the DART cookie enabling it to serve ads to users based on their visit to [www.hitechanalogy.com](http://www.hitechanalogy.com/) and other sites on the Web.

Our visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some of our other advertising partners may also use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include:

  * Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.hitechanalogy.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We have no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad [servers](http://www.ithinkdiff.com/privacy-policy/) for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. You may disable these cookies by your individual browser options. The complete and detailed knowledge about cookies management with specific browsers can be read at browsers’ websites.

 **DISCLAIMER:** The content provided in this site is not warranted or guaranteed by Hitechanalogy.com. The content provided is intended for entertainment and/or educational purposes in order to introduce to the reader key ideas, concepts, and/or product reviews. As such it is incumbent upon the reader to employ real-world tactics for security and implementation of best practices. We are not liable for any negative consequences that may result from implementing any information covered in our articles or tutorials. If this is a hardware review, it is not recommended to open and/or modify your hardware.

[www.hitechanlaogy.com](http://www.hitechanalogy.com/) is not responsible for any kind of damage to hardware or software of your device at all.
